wonderplugin.com 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy | WordPress Plugin

## Privacy Policy

WonderPlugin.com, a service of Magic Hills Pty Ltd, does not gather any personally identifiable data such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address from users of this web site without previous notification.

You may choose to join specific mailing lists for preferred information or just send emails when you have questions. We use Mailchimp to manage email marketing subscriber lists and send emails to our subscribers. [Read MailChimp's Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

Your email address will only be used by Magic Hills Pty Ltd to send replies or messages related to the topic of the mailing list you joined. It will not be sold or disclosed to others. 

When purchasing our product, additional information is needed to fill your order. Any information provided by you will not be sold or given to anyone, and it will only be used by Magic Hills Pty Ltd for filling your order and notifying you by email of updates.

### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information sent to your browser by websites you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work or work more efficiently. Our website uses cookie technology to improve your experience on our site. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information or sensitive personal data.

### Website analytics

Our website uses Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic. Google Analytics does not identify individual users. [Read Google's Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

### Plugin version check and registration

WordPress automatically checks for updates to its core and all installed themes and plugins. When doing update checks, the free plugins hosted on WordPress.org repository will connect to its website https://wordpress.org/ to check for new versions ([Read WordPress.org Privacy Policy](https://wordpress.org/about/privacy/)), the premium plugins will connect to https://www.wonderplugin.com to check for new versions. 

After you have purchased the Commercial License, you will be provided with a unique license key. By entering your license key and registering your website with the plugin, you can update the plugin in your WordPress dashboard. When registering, your domain name, the plugin name and the key will be sent to https://www.wonderplugin.com for verification and registration.

You must keep your license key secret. You may not distribute, give away, lend or re-sell it. We reserve the right to monitor levels of your key usage activity and take any necessary action in the event of abnormal usage being detected.

### Links to other websites:

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
